{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946864938853","data":{"timestamp":" 946864938852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946864944086","data":{"timestamp":" 946864944086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946864950103","data":{"timestamp":" 946864950103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946864953885","data":{"timestamp":" 946864953885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946864960109","data":{"timestamp":" 946864960108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946864963477","data":{"timestamp":" 946864963477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946864969418","data":{"timestamp":" 946864969418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946864979299","data":{"timestamp":" 946864979299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946864985761","data":{"timestamp":" 946864985761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946864989172","data":{"timestamp":" 946864989172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946864992914","data":{"timestamp":" 946864992914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865002925","data":{"timestamp":" 946865002925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865006922","data":{"timestamp":" 946865006922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865010545","data":{"timestamp":" 946865010545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865015607","data":{"timestamp":" 946865015607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865019155","data":{"timestamp":" 946865019155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865024488","data":{"timestamp":" 946865024488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865032935","data":{"timestamp":" 946865032935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865036781","data":{"timestamp":" 946865036781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865040940","data":{"timestamp":" 946865040940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865046029","data":{"timestamp":" 946865046029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865050189","data":{"timestamp":" 946865050189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865054766","data":{"timestamp":" 946865054766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865080198","data":{"timestamp":" 946865080198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865084188","data":{"timestamp":" 946865084187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865089951","data":{"timestamp":" 946865089949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 6df03c91-5fc8-4446-9bea-85a5b496e76f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865105273","data":{"timestamp":" 946865105272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865111269","data":{"timestamp":" 946865111269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865115969","data":{"timestamp":" 946865115969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865127151","data":{"timestamp":" 946865127151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865138403","data":{"timestamp":" 946865138403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865142152","data":{"timestamp":" 946865142152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865146130","data":{"timestamp":" 946865146130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865151000","data":{"timestamp":" 946865151000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865154520","data":{"timestamp":" 946865154519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865160946","data":{"timestamp":" 946865160946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865166807","data":{"timestamp":" 946865166807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865176278","data":{"timestamp":" 946865176278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865181568","data":{"timestamp":" 946865181568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865185265","data":{"timestamp":" 946865185265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865216903","data":{"timestamp":" 946865216902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865221222","data":{"timestamp":" 946865221222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865225670","data":{"timestamp":" 946865225669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865232253","data":{"timestamp":" 946865232253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865236249","data":{"timestamp":" 946865236248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865242016","data":{"timestamp":" 946865242016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865247102","data":{"timestamp":" 946865247102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865251975","data":{"timestamp":" 946865251975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865257887","data":{"timestamp":" 946865257887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865262181","data":{"timestamp":" 946865262180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865271373","data":{"timestamp":" 946865271373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946865277151","data":{"timestamp":" 946865277149"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_050201"," gameId":" 460d8838-d4a0-4b8f-95cf-0a296078b2f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}